Guide to the National Committee to Reopen the Rosenberg Case Records TAM.174
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III. Promotional Materials, 1944-2005; 1975-1997; 12.5 Linear Feet in 10 record cartons, 1 tall manuscript box, and 1 oversize flat box.
  - U.S. Attorney's Office Files: Greenglass' "Secret" Evidence, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Justice Dept. Files: Attempt to Force Rosenberg Confession, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - NCRRC Petitions Justice Dept. - Nov. 15, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - American Bar Association - Defense of Judge Kaufman, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - John D. Lofton, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Patrick Buchanan, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - William Rusher, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Harry Gold, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Kevin Phillips, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Tom Tiede, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Ralph de Toledana, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Richard Jaffe, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Howard Brick, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Henry J. Taylor, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Charles Allen 6/19/53 Article Reprint, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Jim Bishop, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Nat Hentoff, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Morton Sobell, 1967, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Kaufman, 1953, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Alger Hiss, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - William O. Douglas, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Jack Anderson, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Reed Irvine, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Jeffrey Hart, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - National Lawyers' Guild, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - On J. Edgar Hoover and FBI Building, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Activities Abroad, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Organization of American Historians, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Schneir Research, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - FBI Memo: Schneir Story, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Alternative Press, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Contempt Motion Towards FBI by Meeropols -- January '76, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - FBI-CIA, General, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - New York Times Op-Ed - January 18, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - FBI Attack of FOIA - March '76, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Letters to Editor -- Pro, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Letters to Editor -- Con, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Editorials -- Pro, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Editorials -- Con, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Orr Kelly: Julius' "Confession" to Tartakow, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Orr Kelly: "Bizarre Twist" Story, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Orr Kelly: Atty-Gen. Levi's Decision on Access to Gov't Files, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Orr Kelly: Judge Green's Decision on Access to Gov't Files, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Orr Kelly: Prof. Weinstein's Report, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Orr Kelly: CIA Screening of Execution Protests, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Orr Kelly: Greenglass Letters, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Orr Kelly: On Morton Sobell, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Orr Kelly: On Informants - General, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Orr Kelly: Tartakow's Tip on Schneider, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Orr Kelly: Tessie Greenglass' "Verdict" on Ethel, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Orr Kelly: On Rosenbergs' Determination to Remain Silent, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Orr Kelly: FBI Geared for Last-Minute Confession, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Orr Kelly: Hoover's Proposed "Mercy" for Ethel, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Orr Kelly: "Documents Reveal Little...", 1975 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Orr Kelly: New York Times Op-Ed, December 14, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Orr Kelly: FOIA Suit by Meeropols, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Orr Kelly: Justice Dept. to Open Files -- October '75, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - William Chapman: Govt' Attempt to Force Rosenberg Confession (Thru use of psychiatrist), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - William Chapman: Tartakow's Tip on Schneider, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - William Chapman: Julius' Confession to Tartakow, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 90)
  - William Chapman: Waiving of Files Fees, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  - William Chapman: Greenglass' Pre-Trial Change of Testimony, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 92)
  - William Chapman: FBI Geared for Last-Minute Confession, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - William Chapman: Rumor re Greenglass Pre-Execution Recant, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - William Chapman: FBI Kaufman Memo, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - William Chapman: Kaufman Papers, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - NCRRC: News Releases, Activities, and Demonstrations, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - NCRRC: Activities, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - NCRRC: Activities, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - NCRRC: Activities, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Bay Area Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Boston Committee, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Bucks-Mercer Committee, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Cincinnati Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Cleveland Committee, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Kansas City Committee, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Long Island Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 107)
  - Madison Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Milwaukee Committee, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Minneapolis Committee, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - New Hampshire Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Philadelphia Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Poughkeepsie Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Queens, N.Y. Committee, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Springfield Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Vermont Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Washington, D.C. Committee, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Wilmington Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Tartakow Story -- Julius' Alleged Confession, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 119)
  - Tartakow Story -- Julius' Alleged Plan to Infilitrate FBI, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 120)
  - Allen Weinstein, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 121)
  - FBI Files Released to Prof. Weinstein -- August '75, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 122)
  - Files Fees Charged -- FBI and CIA I, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 123)
  - Files Fees Charged -- FBI and CIA II, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 124)
  - Files Fees Waived - FBI and CIA I, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Files Fees Waived - FBI and CIA II, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Justice Dept.'s Efforts to Block Complete Release of Files -- Oct., Nov., Dec. '75, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Release of Gov't Files - General, December '75, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Kaufman Papers: UPI Story 7/11/76, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - FOIA Suit: Release of 725 Pages 8/28/75, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - FOIA Suit: Justice Dept. Promises to Release Files -- November, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - FOIA Suit: Judge Green Orders FBI to Report 7/23/76, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - FOIA Suit: Levi Claims Release of Files 7/11/75, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - FOIA Suit: Tyler Claims Release of Files 8/16/75, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - FOIA Suit: Judge Green Protects Files Aug. '75, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - FOIA Suit: Judge Orders Release or Justify 8/23/75, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - FOIA Suit: FBI Fights to Withhold Data -- July, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - FOIA Suit: Coverage of Filing 7/15/75, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
  - FOIA Suit: Initial Request for the Files Feb. - Apr. '75, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Michael and Robert Meeropol: Speaking Engagements, Interviews, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Robert & Michael Meeropol Speaking Engagements, Interviews, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Michael and Robert Meeropol: Speaking Engagements, Interviews, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Robert & Michael Meeropol Speaking Engagements, Interviews, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Meeropols: GDR Trip 4/76, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Meeropols: Ballantine Tour 6/76, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Meeropols' Response to Tartakow Story Leak, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Meeropols' Charge of File Cover-up -- November '75, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous: "25 years ago", 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous: Films with Rosenberg Reference, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous: Personal Interviews and Monographs with Rosenberg Reference, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous: J. Robert Oppenheimer -- Rosenberg Reference, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous: Sacco & Venzetti -- Rosenberg Reference, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous: Lee Harvey Oswald -- Rosenberg Reference, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous: On the Constitutionality of the Death Penalty -- Rosenberg Reference, 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Columnists, Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous Columns and Editorials with Rosenberg Reference and Letters to Editor, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous: General, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Rosenberg Case - Talks and Discussions, General, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Belgium, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Boasberg Article, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Bob Considine, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Carnegie Hall June 17, '74, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - City Bar Association, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Cuba, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Editorials, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Florida, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Foreign, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - France (General), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - France (General), 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Freedom of Information Act - General, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Freedom of Info Act: Other FOIA Suits, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - French TV -- May 1975 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - French TV -- June 1975 (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
  - French TV -- July 1975 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Alvin Goldstein, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Invitation to an Inquest, 1965, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Life, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Jim Bishop Columns, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - June 1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Kramer TV Special, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - London Sunday Times, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Los Angeles, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Louisville, KY, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Meeropol, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Meeropol Suit for Files, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Memorial Ads, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Mentions, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Mexico City -- UPI, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Michigan Daily, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - MRAP (Movement Against Racism & Anti-Semitism and for Peace), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - New Haven, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - New Jersey -- 1974 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Nizer Suit, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Nizer: Reviews, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Nuclear, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Old French Clippings, 1953-1954, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Old Rosenberg and Sobell Literature, 1955-1968 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - op-ed, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Overviews, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Philadelphia, Pa. Publicity, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Prosecution People, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Rallies and College Publicity, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - "Related", 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - The Rest of the News, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Rifkind and Responses, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Sobell's Exhibits, 1966, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Sobell: On Doing Time, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Morton Sobell on the Rosenbergs, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - St. Louis, Missouri, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Syndicated Pieces and Responses, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Texas Memorial to Rosenbergs, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Village Voice, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Washington, D.C., 1974 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Washington Star Interview July 75, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - We Are Your Sons -- Publicity, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - We Are Your Sons -- Reviews, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Weinstein Suit, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Woods Hole, Massachusetts, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Demonstrations, 1951-1953 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Meeropol, 1953, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Poems and Songs by Edit Segal, 1953, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Denmark, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - East-Germany, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Egypt, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - England, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - France: Paris, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Germany, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - (Hebrew), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Holland, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Hungary, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Italy, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Lebanon, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Poland, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Portugal, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Russia, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Sweden, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Switzerland, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Tunesie, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - USA, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - F.O.I.A., 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Notes for a Pamphlet, circa 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 23-24)
  - Trial Exhibits and Edward Pessen Paper, 1975, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Originals File / To Xerox, 1975-1977 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Pamphlet (M & R), circa 1976 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Newsletters, 1987-1994 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - DDR (Deutsche Demokratische Republic), 1976 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - NCRRC Newsletter, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Release: Nizer Appeal Oct. 13, 1976 / Enclosures (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - July 22 Hearing - Release, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Wash. Star 9/12/76 - Michael, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Kaufman Papers Commentary, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Suppression of News 6/76, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Key Mailing: '76 Kaufman, P.A. Bull. # 12, etc., 1976 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Plays, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Amanda Harris (Newsday Reporter), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Wm. H. Kunstler, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Newsletter Copies, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Misc. Literature, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Nat'l J.W.B., 1976 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Michael & Robby's Op-Ed NY Times - 1/8/76, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - N.Y. Times Article 1/3/76 & Steve's Letter to the Editor Phil. Inquirer, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - "What the Rosenberg Papers Show" N.Y. Times 12/14/76, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - More Article, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - US Embassy - France, circa 1976 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Press Release: Contempt Motion, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Scheir Book, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Article: FBI complains re FOIA 3/27/76, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Arnold Keen - Letter to Editor "Daily World" Cahill Letter to N.Y. Times, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Investigate Judge Kaufman Conduct Petition, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - "The Story of Ethel and Julius Rosenberg", 1976 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Juris Doctor Article, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Coalitions, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Clips, circa 1976 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Sobell Parole - 6/24/76, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Hollywood on Trial, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - FBI: McDermott... "Insane", 1976 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Op-Ed, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Village Voice, 1976-1991 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Slide Show, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - National Coalition Against Repressive Leg. (NCARL), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - NY Times Kaufman Ad, June 19, 1977 (also NYLJ) (Box 12, Folder 60-61)
  - Samples, 1977-1989 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Newsletter, 1977-1988 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Michael & Robby Meeropol, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Sacco-Vanzetti, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - I-C Enclosures, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Judge Irving R. Kaufman, 1977-1989 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Death Penalty Nat'l Coalition vs. Death Penalty, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - New Republic, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Press, 1977-1993 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Rosenberg, 1977-1989 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - The Nation, 1978-1990 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Springfield art. on Kaufman, circa 1978 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Fund to Open Information and Accountability, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - New York Post, 1978-1992 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Press Release, "Rosenberg-Sobell Case Revisited", 1978 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Press Release, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Newsletter Drafts, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - NY Times Documents, 1978-1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, 1978-1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Paul Robeson, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Aaron's report on trip to Washington & Other Aaron Katz, 1979-1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Peggy Dennis, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Press Releases, 1979-1986 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Stern & Radosh Articles (Critique) re: Rosenberg File, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Stern-Radosh, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - New Republic, 1979-1985 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Michael E. Parish, Cold War Justice, etc., 1977 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Articles in Various Papers re Stern & Radosh New Republic Article. June 1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - The New Republic, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Washington Post, 1979-1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Mobilization for Survival, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Morning Freiheit, 1979-1985 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Guardian, 1979-1988 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Newsletters, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Stanley Yalkowsky, circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence and Newsletters, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Newsletters, 1980-1987 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Stanley Yalkowsky Manuscript, circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 23-26)
  - Rosenberg Thesis by Marc E. Berkson, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Jewish Currents, 1980, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Notes on Lehrman Katz Article, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Articles - re 27th Anniversary, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Picasso Leaflet, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Newsletters, and Newspaper Clippings, 1981-1998 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Greensboro Justice, 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Press Releases, 1981-1992 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Commentary, 1981-1987 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - The Atom Bomb Spies H. Montgomery Hyde, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Promotional Materials, 1981-1987 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - NY Times Book Review and Other Articles, 1981-1992 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Radosh The Rosenberg File Articles re Same, 1982-1986 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Ethel Goldberg Appel (Julius Sister), 1982-1990 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Roy Cohn, 1982-1988 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Promotional Material Drafts, 1982-1988 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Dec. 1982 Criminal Justice Hearing (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Telefrance Docudrama Movie Re the Rosenbergs, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Rosenberg Clippings, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Articles and Correspondence, 1982-1989 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Labor Research Association Luncheon Program, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Press Release re: Leo Frank, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 30th Yr, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters and Newsletter Drafts, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Article Drafts, 1983, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Book Review Articles, Newsletters and Newsletter Drafts, 1983-1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - People's Daily World, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - The Ros. File, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - The Rosenberg File by Radosh-Milton, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Article Drafts, 1983-1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Newsletters and Newspaper Clippings, 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - The Rosenberg File, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Conyers, John Congressman, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Town Hall Debate 10-20-83 Articles Covering Debate, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Newsletters and Newsletter Drafts, Correspondence, 1984-1995 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 1984 File (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Correspondence, Newsletters, 1984-1993 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Boston Globe, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Jewish Periodicals, circa 1985 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - NAACP Legal Defense & Educational Fund, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Rosenberg Poetry, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Sol Stern, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Memoriam Notices, 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Newsletters, 1985-1993 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Newsletters, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, 1985-1998 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - 32 Year, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Newsletters and Newsletter Drafts, Newspaper Clippings, Correspondence, 1985-2004 (Box 14, Folder 29-30)
  - Article and Newsletter Drafts, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Newsday, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Newsletters, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence and Promotional Materials, 1986-1993 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence and Newsletters, 1986-1992 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals Michael Meeropol vs. Edwin Meese, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Alfred Dreyfus, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Newsday, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Sentinel / Nat'l Coalition ADP Bryan - RC Cohen, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Newsletters and Event Programs, 1987-1992 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Research Files, 1987, 1992, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Junius Scales, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Voice, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Newsletter Articles and Newsletters, 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Aaron Katz, 1987-1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Articles, 1987-1994 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Article Drafts and Newsletters, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Capital Punishment, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - The Kaufman Papers Pamphlets, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - The Autobiography of Roy Cohn Book Review, circa 1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Annual Commemoration Flyers, 1988, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 35th Annual Commemoration Promotional Mailer, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Article Drafts, Newsletters, Newspaper Clippings, 1988-1993 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Book Review and Editorial, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Rosenberg Era Art Project, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Promotional Materials and Newspaper Clippings, 1988-1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 35 Anniversary, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Jewish Frontier, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - NH Sauberman, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Book Release Ntoice, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Newsletters and Newsletter Drafts, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, 1989-1995 (Box 15, Folder 20-23)
  - Correspondence, Newsletters, Event Programs, 1989-1994 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Article Draft, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - 36th Yr, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Jewish Currents, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - New York Times Articles, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - San Francisco Chronicle, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Lou Shaw, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Fyke Farmer, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Haaretz Article, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Newletter/Article Drafts, circa 1990s (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, Newsletters, Newsletter Drafts, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - 1990 Ha-Aretz, Trial of the Century (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - 1951 Fraudulent Trial Newsletter, circa 1990s (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Newsletters, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Newsletters, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - France, 1990-1995 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence and Newsletters, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Newsletter Mockup, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Newsletters, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - MIT, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Execution Alert, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Today Show Interview, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - The Rosenberg Case Revisited by Jack Gold and Correspondence, 1992, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Article from the French Translated, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Newsletters, Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, 1992-1997 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Article, Correspondence, Press Release, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)